It's been a long time.
Chick-ingle
I guess this is about it.
When a customer takes you,
It's more about balance.
hahaha
An old man who is a friend of a customer
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Oh, wow!
What a lot of image quality!
You set the quality?
We'd like to wait for our guest.
It's just a little bit out of the way here.
Good luck with this.
Please wait until you get to the inside of yourself.
Please wait.
I'll try to pull it out. I'll try to pull it out.
Good night.
If you can't wait, please click on the link
Please make sure to read amazones label.
drieshows Savoy
Free reading Amazones
without the actual touch or
without any credibility
Whisper your voice
Please order
batha4 diese
Singing voice tenant
if you come to us
Link to
For links
Oh! Fun!
Fun!
Image!
20 degrees.
When it reaches 20 degrees Celsius,
Turn off the heat.
Not there yet?
No way to ignore it.
Sometimes.
With a word.
Have it made.
I'll get back to you later.
eyes.
I don't use an otoko, so I'll ask for a cup of milk please.
Soup...
Then, please put vinegar into the cup.
You added vinegar, right? Please mix slowly.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
Gently.
It's getting heavy.
Like a mushroom.
It got really heavy.
Wow, wow.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
I'm sure it will be ready soon.
This much is fine.This much is fine.
Yes, this one is also fine about this much.
This white stuff floating in the white stuff is going to be a cheese called cottage cheese.
Have you ever heard of a clear liquid being milky or whey?
Is it milky?
Like milky or something.
Is it in the ooze on top of the yogurt or something?
Oh, like milky milk.
Yes, I have.
It's the same thing as the whey on the piece.
Yes, and today, since it is made with vinegar, the cottage cheese is a little sour, so we will be washing it with water.
Let's see, there is a cloth at the colander.
Please spread the cloth over the colander.
Please make a slight depression in the middle of the cloth,
One representative will put on gloves,
The finished product is on the ground,
Please open the colander in a circular motion.
Then, please open it,
The person with gloves will wash with water.
I'm hungry!
Wow!
It's so delicious!
The best! The best!
Wow, that's amazing!
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
If you are wearing gloves, please take the ball to the waterworks.
Please be careful with the one with the water below.
Please direct the waterworks to the waterworks, please.
I'm going to let the water trickle out a little bit.
May I try again?
Oh, my God!
Was that a bad eye?
Yeah. - What?
What? Was it a bad eye?
I'm looking forward to it.
Does this mean I can eat now?
They know.
Cracker.
Who has crackers?
I got crackers.
Do you have crackers?
No.
Cracker.
Where's the cracker?
Now.
713 people.
Out of state.
That's a good boy.
I like the way he looks.
I wonder how many hours they've been watching it now.
Have you seen it?
Not now.
I haven't seen it at all.
Mm-hmm. - Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm.
Everyone's looking at it differently now, everyone,
Everyone, it's fun to watch.They are all fun to watch.
Yes, it is.
Finally, there's cheese pork.
Wow, it's so long.
Please wait.
Amazing.
How do you squeeze this?
Like this.
Thank you.
Amazing!
Yunanochi squeeze
I didn't like this one.
Please squeeze hard.
From the screen
The flow from before the delivery...
It's still there.
Is there more of this?
No, there's not.
Come on.
More.
Go, Tex!
More!
Squeeze it! Squeeze it! Squeeze it!
Go, go, go, go.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
You're not strong enough.
That's it.
That's really something, isn't it?
I wonder if there's more.
Are you sure you're okay?
Just a little taste.
Taste it!
Just a taste and it's done.
Taste it.
That's great.
Take your gloves off.
I'm ready.
Rip.
I washed them.
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit.
Cheese!
I want some!
It's good.
Azuki tasting the cheese
Cheese!
Cheese, right?
Cheese.
I ate a cushion.
Maybe it's not tart.
Eraser?
Oh, they're tart?
I've never had an eraser.
They're not tart, are they?
Cheese.
It's not tart, is it?
It's like a watered-down menu item.
It's like an eraser.
This is cottage cheese.This is cottage cheese.
Let's eat it then. Come on.
Quick.
That's great, that's great, that's great.
The cheese is still to be tasted.
The red beans.
Give it to me, please.
Great.
Here you go.
Wow!
There are only two of you left.
Yes, sir.
Before your father.
Please.
Of high school students.
People who want to make it exciting
I want to liven it up
I'm asked if I want to be a part of the excitement
Yes, I do.
Then, please leave
Okun, okun
For your plate of food, yes, please
Cookies?
Yes, I'll have it over.
I miss these cookies.
Thank you.
And the crackers with the cheese.
Yes, sir.
Yourself.
Strawberry jam.
Strawberry jam, please.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Oh, don't get it.
Oh, wait.
That's nice of you.
I'll wait for you.
Thank you very much.
Who wants some?
That's what I'm talking about.
Hey, guys!
Would you like some of our cottage?
Want some?
We're not playing, but it's fun to play
Ta-da!
Would you like some cheese?
If you like cheese, please eat it with salt.
Can I put salt on it?
Yes, please.
Bon appétit.
Where do you put the salt?
On a cracker with cheese and a pinch of salt.
I do wine.
I'm having trouble finding pictures to post these days.
Goodbye.
This is it?
Yes, I'll have one with a sprinkle of salt.
Okay.
Look.Look.
I overdid it.
What should I do?
It's a mountain.
I can't see.
Ready!
Bon appétit!
Here we go.
Eat it all at once.
Oh, it's too burnt.
Too burnt.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You've got to do it in one go.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Ready!
Bon appétit!
I'm hungry.
Yay!
All together.
Here it comes!
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Big mouth!
Yum!
Delicious!
Same timing.
May I?
I waved it in your hand.
Mm-hmm.
Eat again. Why are we us?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm having fun because you guys are having the most fun.
Oh, right.
Bon appétit. Let's do it again.
Oh.
Mmm. Yum. Yum.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
Yummy. Yummy.
I don't think they do it themselves.
Good luck
Please do your best
That's all I've got.
I want you to say
I want our customers to eat it.
It's delicious!
I'll eat it.
I'll have some.
Here you go.
Let them drink with this.
Yes, sir.
You're going to Petappa's solar. You're so cute.
Oh! It's Petappa's fault.
Yum!
Hirogamon made it, too.
I wish someone would write a comment!I wish someone would write a comment.
I have no idea.
I want you to write me a comment.
How do you do that?
We're being robbed.
By Petappa.
I'll give you a push.
Tasty?
It's so cute.
So cute.
Ouch.
Cute.
It's cute.
Delicious.
It was delicious.
I had salt.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Is it good?
Tastes like strawberries.
Yes, it's good.
Cheese is good.
It's rather cheese.
I was surprised to see it finished before I knew it
I know in a moment
Bon appétit!
So it's okay as long as it's 50 degrees Celsius. Adding acid to cold milk doesn't change it at all, but warming it up causes it to separate. It hardens.
It hardens only on the tasty part of the milk,
I think it is good for those who can drink a lot of milk,
I think it is good for those who can drink a lot of milk, but I think everyone can drink it because they are young,
But as you are young, I think you can drink it, but gradually, you know..,
But as they digest it, many of them say that milk is not good for them,
But if you eat it like this,
Do you see how much the amount of milk you just drank has been reduced to the map?
One third.
Less?
A quarter?
A fifth?
A seventh?
One-tenth.
A tenth.
Stop saying increments for a second.
Is that right?
Everything else will be OA.
OA
Dad, we're selling material eggs.
It's a shame.
I'm not sorry, but the house I assembled is not in the house.
It's inside the house.
Thank you for watching.
This one, have it imaginatively sized,
We will also add lemon juice.
Sometimes it will be watery, so we'll have you put it in,
Put it in as you just did.
If I make it easy, can I do it?
If you make it easy, it is a little difficult.
It's a little rough, isn't it?
It's delicious.
The best way to eat it is
Vegetable salad.Even vegetable salads.
Recommendations are a bit interesting
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
Beautiful if you don't buy cloth
Maybe you are a little good at bread alone
I have.
I can do that one too.
Yes, it does.
Don't squeeze it like that.
Like this.
If it's lemon juice...
If it doesn't become sour, you don't have to wash it.
I want to see the powerlessness of it.
I bought a bunch today, so I had them all washed.
They look delicious.
There's a good reason
Congratulations!
Suddenly, it starts right away. Cheese sprinkles.
We'll do this for 19 hours.
Cheese sprinkles
Generative. Generative.
Seven hundred and fifty.
750?
Thank you for watching!
At first, natural cheese is one thing.
Is there any difference between a crosse cheese and a natural cheese?
Yes, I do.
It's really a mixture of two or more kinds of crosse cheeses.
Natural is not mixed.
Yay.
Cool.
I see what you're getting at.
I knew it. It's natural cheese.
Natural cheese is made from cow fat.
It's made from lactic acid bacteria and fast wine.
Thank you for watching.
My process team is different, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Yes.
Yale!
No.
Yale?
Yale.
Tomato of Lee.
Uh, uh, that's what it is.
That's the big difference.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, wow.
Sure, I'll get a job, please.
Maid, please.
OK.
You can go for it.
Hands, be well
Thank you for the food
Thank you very much.thank you so much!
That was amazing.
I thought I was in elementary school.
I thought you were in elementary school.
Maybe I should get a role.
You're so sweet.
That was delicious.
This will make a difference.
I'm right here.
Are you okay?
Don't come in front of me.
You know, I was just...
Just finish up.
You're early.
That was fast.
What's that?
It's a cheese cube.
You can mix it with anything else you like.
And, have you ever had rice with cheese?
Rice with cheese?
You mean rice with cheese?
Rice is not rice.
But you put cheese in it.
Sounds delicious!
It's called Honey's cheese.
Wow.
Amazing!
It's from India or something.
In India, it's called Mosquese.
Mosquito cheese can be boiled, baked, or chewed, but it doesn't melt.
Wow!
It's frozen, but you can melt it in boiling water and mix it with hot soba noodles.
Just mix it with hot soba noodles and it becomes cheese!
But not if it's hard?
Well, it's not hard when it's warm.
If it's cold, it becomes warm.
That's right.
Cold and cold.
Yes, warm and cold are not warm.
It's delicious.
For those of you who are about to eat.
Yes, sir?
I'll try it.
It's a very tasty cheeseburger.
Oh, wow.
Next up...
Crescendo fries, ladies and gentlemen!
I'm not sure if I'd like cheese with a slice of potato as is.
What kind of cheese?
The cheese that's in you.
Yes, um...
Some people don't know if they eat it naturally or not,
If I throw away this wheat,
I have to chew chicken.
Add green onions and fish, cheese and omelette and it's delicious.
Delicious? Delicious.
Yum. Oh, man.
I'm here as a hostage to your uncle.
Oh, man.Eh.
Even hostages, we could ride together and meet the hostages and the guests,
And maybe even have a main steak or something.
You all have one at home, right?
Yes, I do.
Just like this.
Like this.
What else?
I'd like to show you how to eat it,
I think everyone buys hard tapes.
Of course, you eat it while it's still hot, but..,
But, ah....
If it's motor cheese, for example, you can buy gummy bears,
For example, you could give them to your gummy bear,
You can also eat it with a little mustard on the side,
It would have a great flavor and aroma. It is delicious.
You can also use cheddar cheese,
You can also add dried fruits to cheddar cheese,
Mustard or marmalade,
marmalade, potatoes, and so on,
It's delicious with a little mustard, marmalade, potatoes, or whatever.
Or cream cheese,
I like to put it in bread and stuff,
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
Great pleasure.
I had a great time.
It was fun.
That's a good start.
You know, if you work hard at the chef's.
Right.
So, we've started the academic distribution with 10 of them!
Yay!
I'm off!
We started with team building.
But after this, we're going to make a moni...
Moni-making?
No, we're making Twistish.
Twistish?
Twistish.
I'll talk to you about it.
Today.
3:00 p.m. until some time tomorrow. 10:00 p.m.
That's when you're all supposed to be together.
Yes, I knew I had the right place.
First, we're going to the supermarket.
Oh!
And then, uh, crunch.
I'm going to get ready with a crunching joint.
And then we're off!
Wow, this is gonna be fun!
Eat and play?
I don't know.I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know why
I don't know, I don't know why.
I'm going to sleep with him at noon,
Then at 6:00,
I'd take off my costume and go to bed,
I'm going to take a break,
I'm trying to take a break, not wake up,
And then,
As soon as it's over,
Oh, God,
Go to sleep,
And then we can play again.
Then we'll take a bath.
Is there a New York scene?
I got it.
Okay.
There is a New York scene.
New York is OK.
There are only girls here.
After that
Fire
Fire.
We'll fire, right?
We're going to fire
Fire
Certainly hiccups
Certainly
Domestic
Fire
Seriously.
From 2 episodes at 12:00.
Sovsk is in.
2 episodes
Hoo-hoo.
Sort of.
We'll reconvene at midnight.
Not yet.
What the hell?
I'm scared.
But follow me.
We meet again at midnight.
Standing up at night
I'll be wrong in an instant.
And you die.
Rise and shine at 6 a.m.
Radio calisthenics.
I can't.
I can't get up at 6:00 a.m.
Get up at 6:00 a.m.
No.
Shall we watch it again tomorrow?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, yeah.
I have a bad feeling about this.
This time.
What?
10,000 yen for one person
10,000 yen
Now that's what happened to Prince NiseiNow, that's what happened to the Nisei Prince.
That's also 100,000 yen
That's good for one person
Ten thousand each
One is not bad
Ten thousand yen for one
That's not right
This is important too
I'll have some water.
I'll take it to the sensor later.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's gone.
I'm not gonna lie to you. I've been living a very erotic life.
I can't taste it.
Here's your water and your drink.
What?
And a supermarket.
I can't deliver the edible version now.
Not anymore.
Then what will you buy?
Supermarkets and us.
This is the worst.
Yo!
Let's just calm down for now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Let's see what you got
And maybe if you cry
I'll tell you all about it.
I'll grab you.
I'm going to grab you.
I'll stop you where you're concerned
Yes, I'm going to grab you.
You.
Can I talk to you?
You, the customer's business
The customer's business
And when you cry, I'll show you.
I have no money.
I don't have any money.
If you go to the supermarket and find a cash register...
Even if you talk to him...
Oh, what?
I'll get him to do the demonstrations for the toys.
Oh, he said something about that.
Yeah, if they're doing it, then everyone will use it as a reference.
It's a good start, but...
Well, let's go home.
It's called curry.
It's raining today. Normally, we'd have a lot of animals to see.
I'm taking a break.
We'll see a lot of animals when we're done.
All of them.
It's great.
All the fans, all the fans...
Sure, we see a lot of animals.
And the fans.
Yes, for sure
And fans
Today
And fansAnd fans.
I'm thinking of putting the car in the driveway.
Some fans.
I'm sure.
Blue clothes.
And fans
Some fans
Help
I'll help you
When I said par, you said why or why not?
When I said par...
What do you want me to do?
I just wanted a rice ball.
Cheese onigiri.
But it's not too bulky, is it?
Then make me a side dish.
Okay.
Please eat something with me.
Oh, is it okay if I keep it?
Thank you very much.
And now, the last words of the church.
Yes, ma'am.
Smile.
Order
double 。。。。
Thank you very much.
applause
Oho Sou no Yu no Ara
Thank you very much.
Look forward to seeing you next time!
thanks to you
thank you for your hard work
Thank you very much
Oh, and hashtag
Content
Decide
Short
3 characters
It's not like you're suddenly delivering it or something.
4 letters is ideal, that's good.
Right-handed
Right-handedness.
Nope.
19-hour delivery.
19 hour idol
Magu-Magu
What do you think?
19 hours
Northeast 19
That's funny.
I don't get it.
Why don't you just deliver it right off the bat?
Why don't you just deliver it right away?
Suddenly 19 hoursSuddenly 19 hours
Suddenly 19 hours
Yes, we're done.
I hope you like it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for dinner.
Thank you very much
Happy Birthday
Please
Two day squeeze there.
What's a two-day squeeze?
There.
No one does it?
Nobody wants to do it?
Okay, I'll do it.
Two-day draw.
I'll do a two-day squeeze.
Nobody's doing it.
They're back.
This way?
I'll do a two-day squeeze.
I did it. The other day, Dr. Tsuchida's
In the practice room. Please put in CG. Something like that.
Let's go!
Let's go one time.
Let's go.
Let's go!
We're definitely going to do it today.
It's a detail.
She said, "Thank you, Mi-chan.
Really?
You're winning.
Those guys who don't do Shin Shibori...
They were so uptight.
And now they're moving out.
It's a blur.
They're buying so many things.
You got it, Mechi-chan.
I did.
Oh, yeah.
That's delicious.
You're overdoing it, Meki.
Is the picture quality bad?
Maybe it's not the right power source.
Oh, I see.
Meki.
Mekki.
What's that? Isn't she cute?
Oh, yeah, yeah, sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's great if you order this.
That would be great.
Can I order this?
What color can I use?
Turn it off, please.
Can I pay for this with my hand?Can I pay for this with my hand?
Sure.
Here you go.
What do you want?
Can I get some more?
For today.
It's a camera app.
Oh, my God.
It's amazing.
It's like a film camera.
Yeah.
Emo.
Oh, video?
Mm-hmm.
Emmo.
Hey.
I was just wondering.
Yeah, I was.
I'm scared.
No, I'm not.
I love it.
I bought some...
I got you some cheese.
Thank you.
I've got some money on me.
Wallet.
Dorside cheese
Doside cheese.
This was bought by a guy who likes cafe cheese.
Now let's move on to the next bus.
Babies don't have cute cats like poor tits and bugs.
Thank you for watching.
We got our customer's favorite candy.
The candy was the birth of a little baby boy.
Birth!
I forgot to buy drinks. Can I talk to you?
Did you get a drink?
I can't see I bought drinks.
How much further do we have to go from here?
Oh, I can't use it against him.
Oh, watermelon! Sorry.
Watermelon.
It's not enough. Watermelon.
Thank you for watching!
About 15 minutes.
Everyone is free
Free
this
Good night
Good night.
When buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri, when buying onigiri When you buy onigiri, you buy onigiri, you buy onigiri, you buy onigiri, you buy onigiri, you buy onigiri, you buy onigiri, you buy onigiri
OnigiriOnigiri
Thank you very much.
Onigiri
What onigiri?
This is shaved ice with psyllium.
Oh, there it is!
Psy-kids!
I'm so excited!
Did you guys buy it?
I did.
I'm just saying, you should try it.
Let's go back.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Meimei.
Let's go back.
Is this going to be delivered in the car?
Yes, it does.
Hey!
Wow! That's true!
I've never seen anything like it.
Hey, guys, we haven't even said hello yet.
I'm telling you, it's true.
It's a road, just a little further.
Just a little more.
Another staff member.
Oh, excuse me.
This is Minomamsterlast, how are you, Tsutsu-chan, please.
Um, I've already had another song,
I don't often see things like disclosure of information or anything too surprising,
I'm going to put out a lot of information with Hajimaru-san,
What kind of activities are you doing in Tohoku?
Do you mind if I look at you for the camera a lot?
That's totally fine.
Just be natural.
I don't need your voice.
Is it okay if I use my normal voice?
Just your normal voice is fine.
Thank you very much.
Who do I give it to?
Try it.
You're giving it to yourself?
I'll give it to them.
Milk for everyone.
Sweet milk.
I'd like you to taste it now.
Who can drink? Can you drink milk?
I can drink it.
I think I'd rather have mayonnaise.
I can't drink it.
I can drink it.
I think I can drink it.
I'll get out of your way.
Onigiri hot rice balls.
It takes a lot of time.
It's too much!
I could smell it.
They look delicious.
Try it.You should try it.
But this place smells like amazing beef.
You're right. Let's not.
It smells like grass.
I'm not coming.
We'll have something to eat here.
If you do this, you'll be by the diapers.
That's right.
It's spreading.
I miss it.
So, what do we do with these?
It's the same.
Oh, my God.
We're all in this together.
We're all gonna get wet.
Oh, I'm gonna get wet.
It's good to get wet.
I think it's good to get wet.
I'm feeling pretty loose today.
I hope you're all feeling loose, too.
Are you up every day?
I'm getting a lot of hand cramps through the night.
It's not warm or sweet.
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
I don't know what that smells like.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Looks like yogurt.
Let's go for it!
Yummy.
Sweet.
Like cream of cream
But kind of sweet
Delicious
It's my first time tasting it.
It's delicious.
It's kind of refreshing.
But it's like vanilla.
I eat it every morning.
It's all so good.
It's disgusting.
I'm so so so so.
Oh, my God.
It's so good!
I don't know.
Have you ever had it?
I've had it, and it tastes like this.
Opinion.
It's like whipped cream or something.
It's delicious.
I'd like to try this one too.
I surely would.
It's delicious.
Do you sell this?
Yes, we do.
Oh, I see.
It's delicious.
Would you like one?
Can I have a drink?Can I have a drink, please?
Thank you for dinner.
What are you doing?
I'm taking care of everyone.
I'll be watching from downstairs.
This is probably the last one.
That's right.
That's who I'm talking about.
That was delicious.
Well, you can take the car.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for dinner.
We'll be back.
Thank you for the food
Thank you very much
Good night.
I have to go home.
It's raining.
Oh, no.
Oh, man.
Hey.
I'm walking back now.
From now on, it's a letter of wishes.
It's a letter of intent.
It's like I'm giving you a ride, right?
Take this with you.
It's going to be a pearl camera.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm just passing the baton.
You guys be careful with the labels and stuff.
Okay?
I'll close it.
Okay.
This is still day one.
Please.
It's heavy.
Do you want to make it day 1?
No.
That's great.
It's great.
How's it look?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait one more time.
Everybody put your seat belt on.
Thank God the captain's driving.
I've got a runaway. I've got a runner in the back.
Oops, oops, oops.
Did you put your seat belt on?
Did you?
I did.
I also put on my seatbelt.
You are all in the picture, by the way.
I'm going to eat.
Abu, abu, abu. Look, look. Abu-abu-abu.
It's outside, right? That's good.
I could see the skin on her belly.I could see the belly skin.
That hurt.
Please, please, please, please, I'm going to the supermarket.
I'm Ayaka Yasumura, the girl in charge.
I don't know what's there yet, so...
I don't know what they have yet, so let's just eat what we see.
There's a lot of meat and stuff.
Shrimp?
I don't know.
I'm eating a rice ball right now.
How do you like it? Is it good?
Is it good?
It's spicy.
It's got some kind of green chili in it.
Wow, that looks delicious.
Isn't that what supermarkets are for? Candy, drinks, seasonings?
And lips.
No, I was just thinking about what we were doing the other day, and we talked about it the other day, alone, and how much we talked about it.
Please.
I'm talking about the holiday weekend, you know, when we were all alone and we didn't talk about it all the way through.
I'm not going to the end of the line.
I'm not in the mood, good luck with your work, the road may be very bad
I'm not in the mood...
what's with the hashtag?
I think the signal is bad
It's so bad!
I'll raise my hand if you do.
Shit.
It's true.
I know, right?
I'm so rusty.
You can't even see my face.
Even if we all make funny faces now, it won't show up.
They won't give us funny faces for the rest of the show.
You're very brave.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to do it right now, and I'm going to do it beautifully.
Like, beautifully.
There's a guy with a very grandpa skill set, and Lali's sick.
Now there are 900 people.
That's great!
Are you guys free?
It's always raining when we have a long show.
I don't know.
What's with that?
Isn't it the time of year?
Oh, yeah, that's true.
But it was sunny and hot yesterday.
I thought to myself.
Seriously, I think Tohoku-san is the best rain woman.
Yes!
Why?
What?
She's a rain woman, after all.
Seriously? So it's close to Kaja?
Yeah.
Sorry, seriously.
Maybe if we all go to the waterfall, she'll change her mind?So if we all go to the waterfall, will it change the rain girl?
Seriously.
Eh, that's sad.
I thought I was a sunny girl.
I guess you're right.
Let's do it.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I don't know...
It's pretty solid.
The camera for this delivery has some kind of light on it or something.
The picture quality is good, right? Better than usual.
It really is.
Yeah, before.
Wait a minute.
If we stop for 19 hours...
Oh, we just stopped.
When we stop.
It's stopped.
Oh, it's working. It's working.
But that was a long time ago.
Oh, it's here, it's here
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
But maybe it'll be okay again from here.
Oh, but they found it
But I'll probably be okay again from here
Oh, but they found me
I heard you got your tongue back.
You're back? Oh, really? Oh, good, good, good.
You're gonna be okay now?
There's a lot of houses.
People's Wi-Fi.
Okechi-san.
Not the liver
I made a mistake.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know...
Normally, I'd laugh like this.
I shouldn't say that.
No.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know what to say...
It's scary how often you have to say it nowadays.
Oh, really?
So, you know...
I'd like you to listen to me in the background.
Here's the set-up.
Thank you.
Can you explain the height of Yuna's ponytail today?
Please explain.
She's a little spirited today.
High.
Really high.
She's in Akihabara.
Yes, that's right.
It's raining, so it's getting stronger, which is good, because we'll be able to see everyone's pretty faces.
Brazil is cute, too.
They're both so cute!
What are you doing?
What was the last one we did?What was the last one you did?
I think I got it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's not that one.
That one or the three-letter word.
Yes, yes, yes.
What was it?
Three-letter word, young lady.
They're all pretty, aren't they?
I do both.
I do that too.
Wasn't it something else?
What letter vegetable did you say?
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, yes.
Uh-oh.
Like, what song does it start with?
What song it starts with.
What letter
I didn't say how many letters.
I might have.
What was it?
The captain was Shin.
What?
You're right.
He's famous, but he's not a celebrity.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
I'm not talking about celebrities.
I'll give you a subject.
I'll give you the rules now.
What are the rules?
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'm off.
I think I got it.
Good luck with the signal.
I hope you can see it.
I can't get a good picture of the outside.
It's really a forest.
It's stopping, isn't it?
I'm getting a signal.
It's coming.
It's coming. It's coming. It's back. It's working.
Let's go.
The captain is forced to join in.
Both sides are excited.
Let's go.
There you go.
Tamori, the entertainer who starts with his teeth!
He's early!
So fast!
This is strong! Wasn't that amazing?
It's amazing, isn't it? It's great.
Now, let's go to VTEC.
Wow. This is great.
I'm playing a game right now, so I'm sorry if I'm calling you out.
I'm sorry.Sorry.
Well, I'll go next.
Entertainers starting with 2.
Nicce!
Aren't you guys kind of fast?
Wow, it's taking me a while to figure it out.
What is it?
Can I just start with "celebrity"?
Three letters?
I'm going to go with "Shiburi the Entertainer".
Two.
We're done.
Number one.
Once I've said one, I'm done.
I see.
That's right.
The first one to say it wins.
I'd better say the number of letters.
Characters.
But it's hard.
I mean, there are cases where this doesn't exist, right?
Anyway, I'll just say it anyway.
Here we go.
Let's see...
5 letters of celebrities starting with "i".
Osaka
Six letters.
Okay...
It's 5 letters of "い".
IZUMI PINKO
Izumi Pinko
Six letters.
yes
Yes.
Is she there?
Yes or no?
No.
No, I don't think so.
No, they're not here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, hey, guys.
Mr. Mio.
Uh...
Still Mio.
Hi.
I'm Rine-chan.
Mio Imada.
That's pretty hard to do, isn't it?
It's very difficult.
Oh, you mean with Nana Ikoma?
Wow.
And Ito Ran, right?
Ah...
Nannen-chan is Itoran.
Oh, I think she's here.
Oh, wow!
It's right behind here.
Oh, it's moving.
Oh, really? Okay, let's move on.
It stops every now and then.It stops every once in a while.
Looks good.
Well, with all the time we've been stopping, we didn't make it to 19 hours.
Oh, well, well, well.
Oh, here they come.
Okay, I'll go next.
Yes, please.
Well, I don't know.
Oh, well...
Comedians starting with "S".
Satoshiro.
You must be an actor
I don't care if it's an ojikusori.
Rine, you're early!
That's amazing.
I wondered when you'd become a comedian.
You're funny. You're funny.
Next, please bring out the captain.
Why?
What? I'm serious.
He can be a vegetable.
Yeah, a vegetable is fine.
Captain.
It starts with an "A." Vegetable.
Hmm? Acacia?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. She's a celebrity.
What?
Oh, my God.
Senpai!
You're so strong.
I can't answer that yet.
I want to do more.
Okay, here we go. Entertainers whose names start with "na".
Nasuhomi.
Oh!
Nasuhomi-chan.
She's cute, isn't she?
I'm watching Bic Toc Live.
I'm watching
Next.
Yes, ma'am.
Entertainers whose names start with "No.
No!
Hideo Noguchi
Ihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihi
Otokooba
of the hand
Sei
Brush.
wahhhhhh!
Yes and no.
Boober... and animation, too.
Let's make it a good cartoon, too, a cartoon, a cartoon
Not too much, I'm going...
I'll take a cartoon character that starts with "shi" what did you say, I'll take a cartoon character that starts with "shigaraki"?
I'll take Shigaraki and I'll take Shigaraki and I'll take Shigaraki and I'll take Shigaraki...
Shigaraki and Murasan
Characters that start with "ma". Anime characters.
Ma?
Ma!
Ma!Maa.
Malaysian character?
Wow.
Disney.
Let's make it a cartoon.
It's Disney.
Do you want to tie it up?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, for sure.
I'm gonna pin it so hard.
He's a great character.
I'm gonna pin you so hard.
What?
Like a character with a long hair.
You can't do that.
A character with a long hair.
A character with a long hair?
I don't know who that is.
A character with a long hair.
That's him, you see?
Ah, everyone, we've arrived at the supermarket.
Ah...
Is this where we've been before?
Yes, of course.
Oh, no?
Not at all.
But you've been here before?
I know, I know, I know, I know.
This is it, right?
This is it.
Anko.
Anko!
I'm sure this is it.
I know, I know.
It was fun.
There's a police car parked here.
It's too dangerous!
Let's go check it out.
Maybe that's where they live.
That makes sense.
A cop car is a cop car.
Please don't make it so complicated.
That's a great way to prevent crime.
That's true.
No one will come.
Do you have permission from the supermarket?
No.
We're splitting up.
We'll leave them to it.
Don't make an appointment.
I'm not coming in.
What are you going to do, just play audio?
Are you playing outside?
Are you playing?
Well, then you'll have to deliver it inside.
We might have to split up.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I want to go to the supermarket.
I need to buy some water.I need to buy some water.
Buy what?
I suspected we were out of rice, yesterday.
I'll just get a drink and wait for your call.
You want me to give it to you back there?
I'll pick out the drinks. I'm bringing my own.
Money? And snacks?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, you got it.
Money.
Uh, money.
You want to go?
Oh, I don't know.
Do you want to play rock-paper-scissors-paper with it?
Who do you want to go or stay?
I want to stay.
You want to stay?
Yes, I do.
I'll carry your stuff. You want to go?
Yes, I want Yuna.
Yuna, I'm totally going.
Is it okay if I go?
Which way do you feel?
I'll go.
Okay, let's go.
I bought some stuff. Maybe one more person.
Shouldn't we go with one, two, three, five people?
Four would be better.
They're still coming.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, I'll go.
I'm going.
One second.
Okay, maybe just one more second.
Okay, come on.
Can I get you anything?
What would you like to drink?
I'd like something that's only connected to the return.
Okay, well, I'll be right there.
Coke?
Coke!
I don't have anything.
You can buy anything you want.
Candy.
Have you ever had one of those?
Yeah, lawn mower.
That's Sumo.
Sumo?
Does that mean you're buying meat?
I'll leave it to you.
Just one good piece of meat.
And that...
You know those chocolate cookies Kae likes?
I'll get her some.
I heard they're Yasuda-san's food.
More cookies.
Where's Jin-jin?
Chocolate?
It's just chocolate with nothing in it.
Is it bitter?
It's not strawberry.It's not strawberry flavor.
No, it's not.
And fries.
Oh, okay. Black?
Cabbage?
Laco.
Coke?
A big one.
I'll have a nice one.
Cheers.
Okay, be careful.
Thank you very much.
Take a break.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
What do you want to do?
What do you want me to do?
This... this... this inside turtle.
Wait, I'll give it a shot.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Okay.
Wait a minute. I'll give it a shot.
That's great. That's a great camera.
That's great.
You're all grown up now.
You can do whatever you want now.
It's a kid's world now.
But I'm 20.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
How's it feel to be 20?
It's fun.
Have fun.
This is hard.
Can you do it?
Please don't rip my arm off.
But I'm 20.
You wanna come over there?
Yeah, I'm going that way.
I'll go in front of you.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Isn't that it? Karen.
This way.
Okay, then.
Let's do it this way.
Okay, okay.
You see this?
Yeah, it's on.
Oh, my God. I have so much money.
That's a lot of money.
A lot?
He said to hang in there for 19 hours.
Thank you.
But it's only been an hour.
It's been an hour.
So we have 18 hours left.
That's great.
How are you?How are you doing?
Hi. I was wondering if I could ask you a question or two while I'm here.
Like a question about the 19-hour delivery.
Sure.
Hours.
Finally, Yuzuru.
The cheese was delicious.
It was good, wasn't it?
It's amazing!
That's great! They make it at home!
Oh, really?
Your grandma?
Yeah, my grandma makes it.
Hey.
Have you ever had a night out with her? I mean...
The other night.
I don't know how to do this slowly.
With Grandma.
Yeah, yeah.
The day Natsumi went to the concert, she was so excited and happy.
Really? With Waka?
Yeah, the first time. The weather was amazing.
It's your first show. You can sit here.
You want to sit here, too? Sure.
So you want the four of us here? Oh, sure.
Let's make it four here.
Okay, okay.
Okay, so, yeah.
You know, I got really sick after the all-out session.
What? What? Really?
Yeah, there was a mosque on the bullet train.
Maybe we shouldn't go all out.
Ha-ha-ha. It was on my body. I saw the leg.
It would be more fun if it wasn't.
But the other night was the first time we had sex.
Really? Really? What happened?
Oh, uh...
Like this? Yeah.
I was watching a movie, and I thought I saw it on TV.
Is "all" the same as staying up until morning and not going to bed the next day?
I don't know. Even then, I went to bed at 6:00 or so. In the evening.
The next day.
The next day. It was a real all.
It was the first time. I don't know.
That's all?
I wonder how long you guys will watch today.
I wonder what's going to happen.
Nineteen hours.
What if everyone goes to bed?
That's right.
I wonder.
How about the All-Master?
All master
I'll make it all shirts.
That's really great!
Because Miyu, even if I call him in the middle of the night, he'll come back.
She's more likely to come back at night.
He's more likely to come home in the middle of the night.
She won't come home in the morning.
No, he'll come home.
That's great. He said he'll watch till the end.That's great. He said he would see it through to the end.
Wow, that's great.
He said he'll go to bed at night.
Oh, sleeping.
We'll take turns sleeping.
I said it earlier, so it's on the schedule.
Do they wake you up? At night, in the middle of the night.
Sure, yeah.
Night shift.
That's great. An experience.
I'm going to sleep now, right?
If I sleep now.
Sleep now?
How many people are watching us right now?
812 right now.
Close.
Close to what?
Car scrapes in the parking lot.
Talking to myself.
Can you watch me through the night?
818 people.
Sometimes more at night.
That's exciting.
It's kind of big, you know, bowling form guys.
That's fine.
Okay, let's go downstairs.
Okay. - Okay.
What's that? Maybe it stopped raining. You sure?
Yeah, I think so. We did it.
I'll fix this.
Oh, no! I can't fix it.
Whoa! I can't fix it.
Oh, here it comes.
OK!
When you find the big finish line,
When you find the big goal,
When you find the big goal
Oh, this one's good, too
Oh!
Yum!
Thank you for watching!
What a super smiley face!
It's a high dollar.
I can see the ball.
I can see it.
Oh, my gosh!
Nice view.
It's totally fresh.
It's good.
Kiss.
You know what they say...Everyone's predictions.
That's great.
Yay!
One more time.
Oh, my God.
I'm not interested.
You four should line up and do a project.
Sure.
I'll go.
Okay.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
This is so bad.
It's not good.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I need your help.
Advice?
I'm getting a little scared now.
Advice.
Oh, they all looked beautiful in the hall.
Ooh.
Nausarajah's.
This one's just as beautiful.
Maybe we're going in different directions.
Oh, my God. He said I'm not very athletic.
What?
Swimmer.
You're a good swimmer, too.
Swimming?
What do you like?
Backstroke.
That's my least favorite.
The inspiration and the bag you can't pass.
Can't pass the bag?
Inspiration.
One person wide.
Do it all.
Wide.
Dive in first.
yes
Dive.
Oh, wow.
Wow! Your hands are amazing!
Yes.
Oh, my gosh!
That was cool.
It's not cool.
It's not cool. How is it not cool?
The first thing you have to do is jump in like this.
Behind the ears.
This is how you jump.
Do it like this.
Kick it twice with your foot.
Wow! Amazing!
With both feet.
Kick your foot twice, like this,
Oh, wow! Cool!
Like this,
Oh, my gosh!
I'd like to do it later,I felt like doing it later,
I'm allowed to do it again.
Why not?
So we can do it together.
It's a food comforter, isn't it?
Coral's.
Oh, Coral's.
Good for you.
Here you go.
Wave,
All right, three, three,
Oh!
No, no, no.
Why are you looking at me?
It's super fun.
All right, three, three, three,
Why are you looking at me?
What are you doing?
It's fun.
That's funny.
Ariel is amazed.
Ariel is surprised.
She saw the dance store.
That was scary.
Ariel was scared, too.
I know it's there. I'm doing it first.
I don't know.
Thank you for watching.
Mmm.
There's no difference.
Take it.
It must be.
Go, go, go.
Ami, you called for me.
You called for me.
She wants you to do the cartwheel.
You mean this line?
I see.
I can't do it.
It's impossible.
Baseball, there's a lot of sports people asking me to do,
I'm a bowler,
Give me your advice.
Yes, I do.
I'm sure there are people who know bowling.
Can you walk straight with your eyes closed?
What? Bowling?
No, no, no. This.
Oh, I like it.
Sounds like fun.
Okay, let's do it two at a time.
Two at a time?
It's not just one person.
Sure, we can.
Can we do it with just the two of us?
Can we?
Yes, we can.I can do it.
Okay, then. Let's go. All right, let's go!
That's great.
Stop! Line!
Let's walk like skunks!
This is a tightrope walker.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's just skedaddle.
Stall, stall, stall.
Stumble, stumble, stumble.
Sta-sta-sta-sta-sta.
Sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta.
Sta-sta-sta-sta-sta-sta.
Oh, stop, stop, stop.
You suck at this.
I see. It's hard.
Rinne is here.
Oh, okay, then Shinji is here.
Here you go, stop.
It's just a regular Masakyu.
Oh, wow!
What?
Ramen noodles
Ramen noodles.
Regular ramen.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Surrealistic drawing
It's all surreal.
No, it's fine.
Let's stop walking.
What's that? What's wrong with your T-shirt?
What's that? I'm a new member.
We're new members. We are still working on it.
I see.
You're so cute.
Is it raining?
Oh, no.
Clicks.
Hey, hey, try dancing Azarat on purpose. I'm a professional photographer.
Oh, you look great.
Me too?
In the Stryo.
Where do you want me to do it?
I don't know.
Rust.
Sure, sure.
Come on, get into it.
All the way over there, just like this.
Check your footprints
There, there, there, there, there
Don't tell me.
I like your letter. I like everything.
Hey, come on!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Your heart, your body
When you cry
It's the same.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
You care about meMind me.
More and more.
Yes!
Okay, let's go to number two.
Rogue Art.
No, no, no, love me
Love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me, love me.
Oh, that's good.
Which one of you guys is better?
800 people say I'm really good.
Four said you're the best.
Who won?
Oh, I got one that said "Rene".
I got a lot of "Shinshinyo".
Sorry, guys.
Oh, it's fun.
It's fun.
This song is wonderful.
It's wonderful.
It's like a music video.
It sure is.
Which one is the music video?
What song? Should it be a different song?
Sure. What song?
Three sets.
Three sets is hard.
Three sets of forest.
Sure.
I wonder what they are.
But there are at least some songs like that.
That's good.
What do you say?
Stutch?
Oh, yeah, that's a good one. You remember that? Shake.
Much, much, much more.
Much, much, much, much more.
And on and on and on and on.
But what do I do?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
I'm gonna show you...
I'll show you
I'll think about it
I'll think about it.
What? What?
Hey, hey, hey.
Can we dance for our answers?
What? What was that?
Hey, you forgot, didn't you?
What? Is that what this is about? Is there anything like that?
A championship to see who can remember it better.
I quit.
Oh! Mewgaw!
Why are there so many of them?
Oh, no.
Why?
Idiot!
Oh, I'm such a jerk!
Oh, shit.Oh, man.
Oh, no.
I don't even recognize this place anymore.
Ice cream is lighter than words.
Look, ramen!
It's gone!
Ice cream.
No, I miss it.
You still haven't done it, even if you did it once?
No, we haven't.
I think that's the one you haven't performed the most.
Maybe.
Once.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Oh, shit.
You have a pretty voice.
You have a nice voice.
Beginning of love
Love at first.
I'll do it.
Maybe I'll give it a shot with my mom.
I'm not doing it to chum, chum, chum.
Come on, do it.
It's just like Renee's.
Get down on your knees.
Get the cameraman.
Really? Get down on your knees.
Is that okay?
Okay, let's do the mu version of kneel down.
What was it?
Kneel before us first.
The Rinenasi version.
Oh, you remember that one?
I want you to do that one.
I want you to do the one where Rinne gets knocked out.
The Rinenashi version.
Oh, that's funny.
Okay, then.
Get down on your knees.
Good night.
What are they showing you?
You scared the shit out of me back there.
I'm sorry.
It's a different scene.
It's a different stage.
It was great, wasn't it?
You were cool, weren't you?
That, the knack for it.
That was great, wasn't it?
It was good.
It was PDC, right?
It was PDC.
It was great.
They made that.
They told me not to do too much.
But it was more difficult to walk in heels.
It was so beautiful. She was really walking.It was amazingly beautiful. We were really walking.
The four of us are doing amazing things. You're doing a great job.
You really walked the walk. Thank you.
That's great.
We're on our knees.
How's it going?
Good night.
Like the picture will hold.
I know, right?
Mmm-hmm.
What do you got?
Phone call.
It's hard to explain what I'm doing on top of shopping.
Let's go bowling.
On top of shopping.
Yeah, I want to see. I want to see.
What can I do for you?
Oh, are you coming?
Oh, you're coming.
Thank you. Thank you.
Name it after you.
Yay.
I want to do it, today.
You did it.
So let's practice now.
Yeah, let's practice. Let's practice.
I'm doing the ride-high dance.
Wow.
I'll do it now.
Right now?
With the other guys?
Did we do that?
Yes, we did.
Hyper moves.
Yes.
Oh, I didn't do it.
Thank you for watching.
Did we have this?
It's the same.
Maybe it's some kind of...
It's some kind of tour.
It's a samba.
This is it.
Go!
Tele-tele-tele-tele.
That's it.
It's hard.
We did a lot of things at Location Samba.
You did your best.
It was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you for watching.
You have been let in.
Welcome back!Welcome home!
So colorful!
Welcome home!
How was it?
Did you have fun?
It was fun!
Welcome home!
Happy!
What did you get?
How much?
Triple!
We're over number one!
That's why this is such a crock of shit!
I forgot to buy ice cream.
But will it melt?
It's gonna melt.
So I'm gonna have to send you out to get some.
Thank you!
How about bowling tomorrow?
You guys can try.
You know, form.
Forms?
Yeah, you gotta show it to me or it won't show up.
What's that?
The cueing party.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Where are you going?
What? What?
That's where we're going.
Oh, that's where we're going?
We're clear.
What? What?
What?
I'm going.
In the mountains.
But like this.
We'll dry it out.
Hey.
We're also working on the bowling form.
So I'll see you soon.
Teach me how to dress like a woman.
Ooh!
That's great.
What do you think?
It's about 50 there.
Next.
That's money!
Hold it like this.
It's like a slide.
You're going that way?
Do you have one of those?
Yes, I do.There is a type.
Oh, the type of boasting that goes into it.
I see.
That's right.
I have a cold, so I look like a Yankee.
He's not popular with the ladies.
Look at him.
Now, what do you guys think? I'm still working on it. Cup.
Ladies and gentlemen, tomorrow morning, when you watch my Morning Musume. When you watch Morning Musume, guess what?
I guess so.
Please hang up.
Yes, sir.
It flew away with the wind.
It was super fast.
Let's hang them up.
Thank you.
Yes, I did.
I bought so much.
Over there.
You're right.
Oh, my God, you look like a fish.
You sleep in a tent?
Nothing in there?
I saw something.
I mean, they have rice.
The clear kind.
Okay, then.
I'll make fried rice.
I didn't buy any soup stock or anything.
I didn't buy any yakiniku sauce.
Do you have any?
Oh, my God, fish face.
All the time.
And I didn't buy any soy sauce,
Salt and pepper.
Then let's get some yakisoba.
I'll buy chopsticks.
I bought some chopsticks.
But I only had 20.00 in my pocket, so maybe it was too little.
Black pepper and so on.
He asked me to take a picture of the orange one.
I'll show you a close-up of the orange one.
It's cute.
Very cute. Please dance on purpose, on purpose.
Didn't you know? Cute.
Her face is nice. He's so happy because of the quality of the picture.
I still have to buy soy sauce and stuff.
Yes, yes, yes.
But we don't have soy sauce or salt and pepper.
Why not?
And chopsticks. How many chopsticks do you have?
I bought some for you, too.
Ta-da!
I have enough for all the members.
Maybe I'll have some.
Teppan yakisoba, is that okay?
Do you have a teppan?
Teppan yakisoba?
Not net.
It's 1,000 yen.1,000 yen.
1,000 yen?
I'll get yakisoba.
Then I'll get some meat.
Sabrina.
You didn't get the net.
You're on your own.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
I'm just checking now.
There's a freezer in the room.
You can have a glass of water.
Two sips.
Three sips.
It's a good quality picture.
He's super happy.
And I like beautiful women.
I didn't know that.
It's like the Three Lions.
Three's a zipper, too?
Thank you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Watch my phone.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Do you want me to go buy some more?
Please?
Oh, my God.
That was so deliberate.
Just a little scrap.
Scrap?
It has to be scrap.
Paparazzi.
Oh, paparazzi.
I bought a lot of candy.
He said, "Come here.
I'm off.
I think we're missing something.
And grandpa...
Have a nice trip.
I could use some of that.
Thanks for shopping.
Let's get you cheered up.
I'm... I'm... I'm...
Cute! Cute!
Cute.
I only bought three cup noodles.
Seriously?
I'm gonna go buy some more.
But I got chili tomatoes.
Oh, really?
They're cute.
Um...
What are you eating?
Chocolate.
Candy.
What's that?
Pomegranate?
Choco Buckeyes?
Strawberry milk.
Strawberry milk?Strawberry milk?
Yeah, or Palmin or something like that.
Do you eat anything?
Yes!
What?
Ramune.
There's a Ramune kind.
Chocobaris.
You mean you buy them individually?
Not each one, but a box.
Boxes?
Boxes.
If you want one for each of you, you can have one for each of you.
Hey, I don't know what you want.
When do you want it?
Maybe at night? Maybe at night.
Late at night while we watch.
Uh...
Hey, did we buy fireworks?
I did, I did, I did.
Thank you very much.
Can you send me a picture?
Here you go.
I'll give you the money again.
I'll put it in my puff.
People are asking for azukisuba in the comments section.
It's a cute picture.
Okay, so they're happy.
I'm taking selfies.
I'm going to put it in the Uraaka chat room.
That's great!
I'll put it in the Uraraka chat.
What's your favorite Uraaka?
What are the contents of your fan club?
What is it?
Do people ignore this?
Can we see URAAKA while watching this?
Do they get together and watch it?
Eeeee!
This is Unaoka chatting.
It's Unaoka.
She's cute. Karaoke and stuff,
Karaoke?
I got a notification.
Did you rent it? The camera.
Yes, I did.
Did you lend it?
Okay, I'll take the pearl camera.
Pearl camera.
I'm looking at them from my point of view.
Yes, sir.
During the seat, the front is always heaven and earth, and these two are fighting for the haraungachi.
That's right.
It looks like Pearl won today.
Hai.
I will put them on the back red together now.
Yes, I didn't take a picture of the cell phone screen, so don't worry.
You know, she's very cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
Yes, it's cute. Really.Yeah, it's cute. Really.
In close-up,
Oh, yeah?
Well, can I make that bijou time one time?
How do you do it? Up.
Just give it a quick tap.
That's great.
But, you know, at this distance, you've got to be up,
Just a little bit.
I said, "A little bit.
Ice cream pears.
What?
Ice cream.
Oh, that's cute.
Kil-Kil.
Oh, he said Sacre.
Okay, well, tell him I'll do it.
Did you guys pick? The girl in the back.
Oh, he's so cute.
Oh, really?
Wait a minute.
He's so cute.
Thank you.
The three of us.
I'm going to look at Rine's face while I do a close-up.
I'm fine. I'm fine. I have good art.
You're so cute.
Yes, I do.
You have it?
I said you have it.
They're making some kind of bread.
He said, "Do you have that bread?
What bread?
Melon Suder, Vanilla Lover.
Melon Suder, Vanilla Lover?
What else? Are you okay?
I'm gonna close it all up.
I'll leave it to you.
Aren't they adorable?
Oh, they're from the cat family, aren't they?
Okay, I'm good. I'm good.
The ball thing.
The ball thing?
Lun-chan's.
And one pear from the ice cream cone.
That was amazing!
The one with the beejunas was amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's just that when someone holds a camera to my face...
I'm so conscious of it, I make a peace with it.
That's nice.
It's always been like this.
If I press this, it's good, right?
It's okay if I press this one.
You don't want to turn this off?
What's this one?
Here.
Can I push it?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How do I turn this off?
What?
It won't go away?
What's the difference?
I think I'm gonna have to make a piece of that.
Hey.
You're really looking at it from the members' point of view, aren't you?
Yeah.
That's the usual look.
That's the way they look at you.
Linek's point of view.
They're all sleeping, so their heads are sticking out a little bit here and there.
Oh, he's back.
Welcome home.
Rinec's point of view
Good morning
Welcome back.
I'm filming.
Good night.
How was it?
It was super.
Was it cold?
Not at all.
It was cold for me, too.
No colder than yesterday.
It was so hot yesterday.
Yes, it was.
We're in trouble.
That's embarrassing.
Well, then, do you have something shiny you'd like to say? I have a quince, eh?
Oh, thank goodness.
Thank you, super.
Thank you super, let's go to this super next time.
So cute!
She can do this! So cute!
I ate them one by one when I was in elementary school and they were shockingly delicious!
Sapporo fries.
Heh.
There's enough for nine people.
I'd like to share it with my friends.
Yes!
Okay.
Oh, it's really nice when you take a picture from here.
So cute!
Through the gap
Is this a camera outside now?
Turtle outside.
You always have a camera outside?
I'm updating it.
Is that my hair up?
Aah!
It's so hot!
I wonder who that is.
Nice. This shot is really good.
I can't wait for him to turn around.
I'll tell you.
Run-chan, take a look at the four of them.
Wait a minute.
That's good.
Here we go. Look forward.Let's go. Turn around.
Turn around already.
What? What's this?
It's so good!
This is great!
Let's make the same face together.
What?
I thought we were turning around...
Oh, I'm right on topic! I'm on topic!
Are you saying it?
Oh, wait, let's do that face.
Okay, let's just do that for now.
Ouch.
Piggybacking!
Okay, okay.
Ready?
Please, please, please.
Turn around already!
Oh, he's having lunch.
Don't take it too hard.
Oh, I got it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's not that I got it, it's just that you're cute.
I was just like, "Yes, I got it.
That's what I said.
You're cute.
You're a coach.
Cute.
That's nice.
I'll be right there. Rock, paper, scissors, pie.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
What was that?
I'm just trying to fill in that spare time.
Oh, thank you. That's very helpful.
I miss comedy.
Come on, it's so much better than that.
I said that a lot earlier.
We were just shooting a music video.
Mom.
Mom, tell me.
I can't!
You want to hear about centrifugal force, don't you, guys?
I'm back.
He's back! He's back! He's back! He's back!
Rinri Yasuho is back.
Thank you.
I have to go quickly.
I have to.
Thank you.
I'll scan it and eat it.
Please.
One hundred kilometers.
They'll catch us.
We'll get caught.We're gonna get caught.
They will?
Come on out.
This looks like a musical instrument, doesn't it?
Boo.
Everyone's a little tired.
It's a little early.
I think maybe everyone is tired.
I wonder why.
But I can tell. Because it's raining.
That's for sure.
The sun isn't losing to the rain at all.
Really?
I'm like, everything goes to shit when it rains.
Is there anywhere far from here?
A little more.
The sky.
Pretty.
Cute.
She's cute.
It's like a beauty explosion.
So cute.
When you make a close-up of this, you know, it looks beautiful.
I can do close-ups.
Isn't she pretty?
She's got a strong face.
I like that.
Oh, okay.
Okay. Here's a sneak peek of me taking a picture.
Morning, Morning.
Good morning, morning.
I wonder what kind of comments I'm getting.
Let's see...
A beautiful woman's explosive delivery.
I can tell she's got a strong face.
Lun is nice too.
How many times a day do people say she's cute?
The picture quality brings out even more of Touhoku-san's beauty
You can't go wrong with a face
Good morning morning
I feel like a visiting nerd.
At least I read the whole thing.
Thanks for commenting.
And...
And thank you.
He said we should have a good morning championship.
Let's do it one at a time.
What's that?
I'm not good at this.
You're not good at it.
Let's do it during the show.
Let's go higher than the first person's
Let's go higher than the session.
Oh, I see.
OK.
Let's start with Mr. Yatsumoji.
Good morning, Mr. Yatsumoji.
Please turn around for a moment.
Good morning.
He's going to be very excited.He's going to be very excited.
Good morning. - Good morning.
That's good, because it's the first one.
That's good.
Okay, what's next?
Next.
Okay, let's go here.
Good morning.
Come here.
Shinju-san.
Wait a minute
But you have to go beyond the kaya
Kaya has to go over
No... the Kaya is beyond...
I know, Shinju.
Good morning
He said he'll be back next time.
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Utsura, let's go first ok, now let's go to Sakurai's
He's on a roll.
Fumi-chan says one more time.
Okay.
You've got a good head start.
Let's go.
He's back.
Here they come.
Come on!
Here we go.
I'm going.
You're early.
Not too fast, right?
You know what?
I'm modestly overweight.
Good morning!
What's the weight?
There are three of us left.
Good morning!
Karen!
Good morning over 2!
Oh! Good morning!
No good.
Oh!
Say it bigger and mean it!
Good morning!
Isn't this important?
Which one do you want?
Which one, which one, which one, which one, which one?
Which one?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Here we go.
Ahhh...
Yaaaah!
Big, big, big!
Camera work is important!
It's the last one.
It's a risk to be the last.
I don't know if I'm going to be the loudest... or the loudest I've ever been.
Here we go!
Let's go!heave-ho! - heave-ho!
Wahhh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Wahhh...
Wahhhhh...
That was amazing.
That was so cool!
I've never heard that voice before.
I thought you'd broken my biomechanical system.
They think I'm Rune-chan.
I've never heard that voice before.
If they think it's Runchan's voice...
They thought so.
She called me an uncle.
They called me "Uncle".
CV Mr. Lucky
You've been doing this for a long time.
CV Lucky
Congratulations on your exclusive debut.
Thank you. It's my dream come true.
I'll have to make him do the captain thing.
Captain?
Captain, good morning for the last time, please.
Good morning. - Good morning. - Good morning.
They're uploading the captain's stuff right now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's a good-lookin' surprise.
I want you to watch it. I want you to watch it.
It's a good-looking surprise!
Captain's nape.
Captain, if you could move your ears or something...
Ears, please.
I'm the captain!
I'm the captain.
Like you don't need to see it.
Captain, you're gonna make me cry.
Is the moon coming?
He said it'll be here soon.
It's still far away.
What happened to you earlier?
What happened?
I'll see you the day after tomorrow.
What? It wasn't fixed yet?
Yes, thank you.
Oh, regular.
That's great.
A little highlight for me.
Why is it the highlight of Paris that I notice the most?
In front of Tose and Stance, after all.
I'll give you a present.
For real?
A penlight, like a pair of magic hands.
Mago no Te penlight.
Nice camera work.
Thank you for the great expressions.
Look! Hamster!
Hamster!Hamster
hamster
Cute.
I'm going to get you all drunk.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
Stop, stop, stop...
I challenge you to see how many times you can get drunk even though it was 19 hours ago!
LOL!
This is the worst!
Oh...
Oh, were you taking pictures? Shinjuku-chan's photography course.
I'll try my best to give it to you on Instagram! Please do!
Captain, you're getting stronger.
Don't take my picture!
He's so cute!
Is anyone else saving Kirito's arms and legs?
I sure do!
I want them so bad! I want to save Kirito's hands and feet!
Please give them to me. Interesting shoes and stuff.
There's a lot of stuff in there.
Oh my gosh!
This is definitely where I wanted to come!
Yeah, that's why Yuu also sent me this when she saw it.
Amazing!!!
Come as a couple, people. There's a heart.
How is it going to clear up?
It's gonna clear up now!
They want to say, "It's gonna be fine now.
It's gonna clear up now.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
What the hell is that?
Don't say it.
Oh, no.
Do you know the weather record?
Oh, yeah.
It's bad if you don't know what it is.
You don't know the weather record.
But it was cloudy.
But it was raining.
Where was it?
I can't tell you.
Yes, ma'am.
Rhino.
Kidnapping.
Are you going to unload all your stuff?
Unload?
Look at all this stuff.
It's not for dinner, anyway.
It's the delivery room.
I'll just have an ice cream.
There's a lot of ice cream in here.
I'll just take this.
And there's some sashimi, too.
She's so beautiful.
She's really cute.
This is so good.
That's a really nice package.
It's really nice.Seriously good.
Everyone in the field.
Grab your stuff.
Let's go to the baggage room first.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to leave it with you, wouldn't you?
Room.
I'll take this with me later. I'll get the camera.
I'll take it. I'll take it with me later.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I'd like to go to the luggage room.
It's a lot of private stuff for me.
Oh, and do you have umbrellas for everyone?
There's a few umbrellas.
Okay, we'll go in. We'll go in together.
Yeah, we'll go in together. Okay, let's go.
There it is!
It's close.
Windshield, windshield.
I'm just gonna stab here. Okay.
I'm just gonna stab you right here.
Lilacmo, isn't it?
Lilacmo.
Grownups!
Where did you put it?
I'm leaving it in my pocket.
Thank you. Next to my cargo shorts.
I don't mind.
You should put an umbrella under it. It's not too far.
Can you get it?
Umbrella. Your umbrella.
That's nice.
Sorry. Thank you.
Do you live in a tent?
Yes, but I'll introduce you as I go.
Let's go in, Yasumori.
Let's all go in.
Thank you very much.
But there will be no one left in the corner.
I'll use my voice to agitate the audience, so I think it would look better if you all go in front of me.
OK.
Straight ahead.
So, do you mind if I get drenched?
Yes.
Chikamori.
Amazing.
Wow, I saw that in a picture.
I'll give it to you.
Here you go.
That's so delicious!
Oh, my God.
The very back.
You don't have a carry-on case today, do you?
I don't have a carry-on case.
It's amazing. It's a great Paralympic Games.
That's unusual, isn't it?
You didn't bring a change of clothes, did you? I have a theory.
That would be fun.
Really? I did bring a change of clothes today.No way. I'm bringing it today.
This is...
Oh, look, they're calling it a "carry on" at the campground.
No, we're not. We're...
No one's in the picture right now.
My luggage...
To the Lev...
Oh!
I want it taken.
Look at that.
It's okay.
You're so cute.
I'm so embarrassed.
I wish it would clear up.
I can't get it to clear up somehow.
This cloud cover isn't going to clear it up.
Let's get our stuff for now.
That's Miyu's top.
Got it.
One hundred points.
You can put your luggage in the back.
That's fine.
No, it's not. This is like a luggage compartment.
It's not like nine people sleeping in one room.
We're already using this room. I don't know if it's all of them.
Sleeping quarters. This is luggage storage.
I don't want anything in the picture.
Oh, it's raining.
We're both here to make a difference.
It's between the two of us, so it didn't make much sense.
It's so cute!
Wait, please, look at me.
Oh, he's so cute!
It's so cute!
Seriously cute.
You're really good at art.
I'm thinking about it again.
Not at all.
We're talking. We're in the middle of a strategy meeting.
Everyone cut this out and put it on TikTok.
Not for makeup.
Please put it on TikTok.
Let's go, people who put their luggage down.
Okay.
Did you put your luggage down?
Yeah, I know. I wonder how much luggage we've got.
I don't think I know.
So we just put everything down for now?
Yeah, I just need my cell phone and stuff.
I just got my phone.
Here, take it.
I brought it because I thought Yasuda-san was a member.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay.
Watch out! Thank you.
Thank you.
Young exclusive photographer
Hey, that's not good.
I'm shooting now.
Sorry. It's raining.
Room tour?Room Tour?
Take a room tour.
Room tour.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're invited, sir.
It's so cold in the rain.
It's cold.
Why don't you put it outside?
It's gonna get really wet in here to begin with.
Maybe it's here.
Maybe it's inside here.
That didn't make sense.
It's still good, right?
Sure it is.
Sure.
Seeeeee!
Smells good. Smells like chikuwa.
Excuse me.
It's so good.
This is our room.
Yay!
This is the Grand Prix room today.
I saw the mushrooms.
This is amazing.
This is going to cut off the planetarium or something.
Even during the distribution there and there.
Wow! A planetarium.
Me?
It's so good.
It's super nice.
It's got a microphone and a Jacuzzi.
So let's dive in.
Is there a New York scene?
Yes, there is.
Is there?
You guys have to be watching. There will be a New York scene.
There might be.
Cute.
It's amazing.
Is it good? New York scene.
It smells like a new house.
Yeah. It's a new house.
If it were sunny, you'd definitely see a lot of cows and stuff.
Somebody please stop the rain!
Well, take a cutter and cut around it.
It's all coming down, isn't it?
That's amazing.
You're so cute.
Is it sunny?
I hope so.
Are you gonna sleep?
Oh, my God.
It's sunny.
I wonder if there are any fireflies.
Simon, isn't it?
I think so.
We can take a nap in the summer.
Let's do it.Oh, let's do it.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
I wanna go in!
How do you do that?
Aren't you supposed to eat in there or something?
Oh, my God, can you see it?
Are you looking too much?
I know, I know. I'll look.
But we're the only ones here today.
Where are you guys going to sleep?
This room. That room is the one we don't film in anymore.
Sleeping hard. No, sleeping hard that we don't want to be in the picture.
Cute.
I'm leaking. I'm leaking cuteness.
Only in the shooting room.
There's only one of them. There's only three of them.
Hmm?
So cute.
My goods.
Karen is cute. Rineko is cute.
Cute. Good!
Crow stands up, too.
Kasaki, do you want to see the visual?
Always good.
Are you okay? She's really nice.
Are you serious?
If I don't see it, I'll have it cut out.
Bye-bye.
What? She was cute.
He looked like a boo.
He's cute.
He was an old man.
He's a Yankee.
Oh, no, I can't do it.
Hello.
My gal is shy.
She's shy.
Wow.
Hmm?
Money. I thought it was money.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God! It's all bugs!
Let's roll the bugs.
That'll get rid of the bugs, right?
It's now pudding. By the way.
All right, guys, let's go.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Hey, I want to take a picture.
Oh, that's nice.
Very nice.
Let's get some insect repellent.
It's so cute.
I'll send it to you later.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What's that thing you call shushing?
If you're in trouble, just dance on it.If you're in trouble, you dance like that.
If you're in trouble, you dance that.
You earn your checks.
I'm just relaxing like this.
What just happened?
I thought my mom would go wow, so I went live and she went "go".
It was pretty high. I was thinking, but I glanced at it.
PG.
Eh, wow.
Kebro.
Don't do it.
Yes, Mr. Yonny.
Just a little cell phone.
This is how I take pictures.
What did you film, by the way?
Does it show up?
Yes, it's on the camera.
I'm filming.
Like you're good at it.
Yes, she is.
She's cute.
It's cute.
It's good that it looks like an off-shot.
It's nice.
I tried to capture the moment of taking the picture.
It's good.
Then lower your face.
Oh, summer?
Not this one?
Now, what's this Tournedos going to be used for? I'm looking forward to it, gentlemen.
I've been getting your comments. What's it for?
Well, you can stay.
Well, it's business.
Don't say that. It's a memory.
Finally, the nine of us.
Close the door!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
Anything you want!
It's a bed now.
All of a sudden.
Put it here or something.
Oh, he wants me to open it.
He's here.
I'm going to build a snowman.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
I did it!
Here it comes.
This is fun.
It's open.
It's okay.
There's nobody here.
I'm scared.
Don't be so calm.
There's nobody out there.
Here they come. Here they come.
He's so cute.Cute
Nice cute
Conan the Man
Insect Conan
this might be good
good night!
There's some light here.
That's nice.
It was so pretty looking this way.
Here's your hair dryer.
Today's hair dryer is a Panasonic.
This is a Panasonic.
Let's make a snowman.
Here's a cup.
Here are some tissues.
Day three, he gave it to me as a present.
Here's the fixed point.
See you later.
Okay, let's do dance time.
Yes, please.
Okay.
Dance time!
This way or the other way.
Cute.
Now that's emo.
I'm hungry.
I can eat now.
Mommy.
Mommy. Mommy.
Mom. - Mom.
No, not you.
I'm hungry, too.
Ami, Mommy.
Ami's mommy.
Who's Mommy to?
You win, you lose, you lose.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'm going to ask you to eat.
The loser asks for dinner in a baby voice.
I don't want to lose!
I'm kidding.
Are you copying your mother?
I'm not your mother.
I'd like to get acquainted with you if I could.
Hello?
You're really doing it.
You're doing it.
I want you to do it.
Okay, okay.
Okay
Seishan danchon rock-paper-scissors-scissors!
Aiko, right?
It's aiko, right?
We decided today, right?
Yes, this one, right?Yes, this is it, right?
Wow.
What, what, what, what?
Did I win?
Okay, let's have the chokis.
Choki, who?
Choki, gather around, please.
Wow.
Who's there?
You're Babu, right?
That's right.
First, goo.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Wow.
What do you think?
And that, too. April 22, 1996.
January 19
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
what a sound antia the voice in the take IG nice
orid29
I can't get it already
ia
more than 100
more than 100.
Riwaka's place
I was told that the amount of shoes was egregious
I was told the amount of shoes was egregious.
This is bad, isn't it?
There are shoes there.
We don't sell them.
Discontinued?
No, they're not.
Well, let's see who's here.
Let's go say hello.
Let's go say hi.
I'll be right there.
What? What? Is this, like, a place where they cook for you?
No, no, no, no, they cut up the meat and stuff, and you cook it yourself.
There's no grilling.
Okay, let's go say hi. You haven't been. Let's go say hi.
Thanks for the comment.
You know, I keep forgetting who's going to be there.
I got slippers.
You don't need crocs, do you? Say, "Let's go home.
You can do it.
Right now, right now.
They're better in Crocs. It's easier.
It's easier. It's easier.
Crocs, please.
Four?
No, thanks.
Okay, let's just put these shoes in the car. They're in the way.
Sure.
Let's change in the car.
I said bye-bye shoes. Here.
Let's just go into Juchee.
Close, close.
Close. Very close.Close, very close.
Very close.
Very close
Kaede hates putting up umbrellas.
I'll let you in.
Go say hi.
Say hi.
Go to the car, change your stuff, and come back.
Let's go, everyone.
Come on, guys. Let's go.
This is how it works... you split up into the fast movers and the slow movers.
Upducci's cute.
It says "adorable.
I hear it's adorable.
I want to do something more fun.
It looks like it's snowing, doesn't it?
Yeah, it sure does.
It's like living in Kamakura.
Oh, wait, I got automatic Crocs.
Crocs!
That's our manager, the Shido Enemy Manager.
What?
They're here.
Because of what you said on the news feed? That's what I'm talking about.
That's great.
You're not wearing them?
I'll wear them. I'll wear them.
Put them on.
Did you laugh?
I'm not wearing them anymore.
Something Seyan washed in the park.
Where are they?
I heard Sejan washed them in the park.
I'll talk to him again.
Why don't you hurry up and put them on?
How dead are we?
Then they will, too.
The other side?
Are there people over there?
Shouldn't we go out or something?
Well, well, well. Seyan did his best to wash them.
Shut up.
Here's your Crocs.
Good night.
Anyway, it's okay, right?
These black shoes are about 3 cm too big.
Can we all wear black shoes?
Oh, they're good, right? They're good.
But I'm more interested in the color.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have a lot of them off.
Well, you know, shiny.
I'm gonna put these shoes on these shoes, too.
Where do we put these shoes?
Oh, you can just put them in there.
These shoes are very important.
Put them in the pond.
I'll put them in the pond.
Maybe I should put them on barefoot.Then I'd better wear them barefoot, perhaps.
Manneh.
Manneh 3rd grade
Manneh was in third grade.
Oh, yeah?
What's your brother?
My brother is your sister.
It's hard with the rain, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
What? Manneh, really?
My brother is your sister.
Actually...
I tried Miyu.
I see.
From now on...
You're all going to do this?
This is Miyu, and that's...
Pearls?
That's what I'm going to do.
That's me.
That's right.
I'll make these into pearls, and this is Miyu.
This is for the captain.
Oh, what's wrong?
What? What? Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
And pearls, then I'll give this to the captain.
Oh, okay.
Is that right?
But the captain...
Whose is this?
You're the captain.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's not?
Whose?
Well, let's go say hi.
You don't want to go say hi?
This isn't Iosano, is it?
Probably not.
Just put yours in there for now.
Let's trade.
Do you think it'll fit?
It's huge.
Someone's ringing the bell.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go, go, go, go.
Your girlfriend's doing it alone.
You should do it with her.
Runchan.
Why are those two just looking on? I'm doing this alone.
I won't do it with you.
Are you the creepy type? For now.
Let's say hello.
Let's go say hi anyway.
Punk it. Thanks.
Cheating.
I've been called a flirt.
I want to go over there.
Okay, let's go.
I'll take that one.I'll go with that.
Ami and Tsapaia...
I just laughed my nose off.
Let's go in.
Oh, my God.
Excuse me.
Yes, hello.
May I say hello?
Yes, please.
Put your umbrella down.
You should turn your head this way.
Yes, sir.
Are you in?
Nice to meet you.
Ichiro! Ichiro's stylists are Rinabito and Sana-chan. Pleased to meet you.
Please take care of him.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
About the time of the dinner, is it okay if we have dinner in 30 minutes or so?
Yes, I'm fine.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
Let's go home.
Yes, the amenity buffet. I haven't shown everyone the one I got separately earlier,
But it looks like there's another buffet.
A buffet?
Amenity buffet.
And we all received a bottle separately.
There are so many amenities.
Bodkin toppings and other stylish things.
Soap bubbles!
Amazing.
There are so many.
There's a link.
It's nice.
You should put up some amenities.
That's great.
It's like this.
I'm gonna have to get one of these.
I like this.
I got that one.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
I bought it yesterday.
Then I don't want it.
We can all eat here.
Oh, yeah.
I've been skipping this one.
It's funny.
Nana-bun-bun-bun.
Seven hump, seven hump, seven hump, seven hump.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, ma'am.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm just relaxing.
You want some snacks?
I'm going to have a snack.
I'm going to eat sweets.
I'm going to the kitchen!
Sweet potatoes are all here.
Not sweet potatoes?
There's a puddle.Puddles.
Here we go, puddle.
This water, the puddle.
Let's do more, guys.
Thank you. Thank you.
You okay? - I'm fine.
I'm doing it this way.
Is that good?
Is it okay?
Oh, no, don't film Kae.
I don't want to.
I don't want to be on it.
NHK!
I'm being filmed so hard.
Here's the transmitter.
Distribution equipment is here.
I wish I could come here in private.
It'll be fun with my family.
Yeah, it'll be fun.
I'll make a suggestion.
Momma...
Mamamamia!
Oh, my God! Did we go in there?
I think that's it.
Not here.
What's that? I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
He's going that way.
We're having dinner over here.
Dinner is this way.
But we're not supposed to wait here for a half hour, are we?
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, but there's something about the captain making himself at home.
I'm curious.
Isn't that the WC?
The WC?
That's it! ShowerCom.
Oh, the shower.
This place has a butt like a swimming pool.
Rain's a bitch.
Oh, we'll do it here.
Captain, there's a camera.
But do you want me to set it up?
I'm just gonna go in one time. Okay.
Okay, bye.
Oh, my God, I've got a bedazzle.
Oh, shit.
Wow.
Emo free.
What?
For now.
Was that dinner?
It's time to play. Time to play.
I don't care if I don't get the shot.
So, you have a fitting in half an hour?
Fitting?
About. About.
I'm having dinner in 30 minutes.
It's 10 pieces of rice.It's 10 pieces of rice.
The chairman of the cleaning committee of the Japan Cleanup Committee is turning umbrellas.
He seems to be turning umbrellas for cleaning. What kind of umbrella category is this?
It's a surreal picture.
It's cleaning more than usual.
And the Japan Rabbit Chair Committee.
Should I put this preparation out or is there something I put in?
You met Usuka Kusaka, right? Because it's the first time in 5 years.
It's raining today, isn't it?
But, you know, it's okay from our side, right? I think it would be better if we hadn't seen each other.
Then I think it's okay to cheat on her.
I would forgive him.
Forgive him.
You don't have a choice.
You'll see her next month, right?
Yeah, in Sendai.
Suddenly TikTok is on.
Anemic, old bride.
What's this?
Oh, I didn't see it before.
It's an appetizer.
Is it really delicious?
We'll put the sauce in this bowl after you eat it,
Wow! How stylish!
It's served in a rabech.
What is this in the middle?
This is a bamboo shoot.
Stumps?
This is a rabesch.
Laveche!
Lavish!
It's so cute.
Amazing.
Eh, why not?
Eh, cute.
Cute!
Surprise-don't-please.
I've uploaded the part where his teeth are all dark.
His teeth...
Okay, I'm sorry.
It's funny.
When is everyone going to drink soy milk?
I want to drink soy milk!
Oh my God, we went through a lot of play-doh.
So, do you want to take one or the other?
What is it?
Oh, it's a litter!
That's the third one.
Here we go!
Oh, my God.
That's so cool!
Can we put our drinks and stuff over here?
Oh, sorry, Kaya-san.
Kaya-san will take care of it.
Okay, okay.
I'm looking at it from my point of view.
It's a member.
Thank you very much.
Please look here.
Let's decide on that.
Like the insurance guy.You know, the insurance guy.
Watchman...
Chill guy.
Leader.
What did you say?
"Chill team leader.
The leader.
How's that?
Insurance.
Dinner.
I want to go to the live end.
I still want to go once on Spring Day.
I haven't done anything yet.
Yes, I have.
Runchan
This is
Inari Higashihiro's
The oldest, Hikaru Rockett.
Rabbit Magical Girl
Almost to her birthday!
This way
Sakura Hina's
wife
The only one now
Bob girl!
She is a very good singer!
This is
Pearl Kitxe.
She loves comic books!
This is
Yuna Hazuki's
back view
Congratulations!
Ah!
She's a very bright girl
This is a gal's back view
This is
Kozuka-chan is wacthing.
This is Mr. Date.
He's trying to introduce something.
I recommend this one.
What is it?
Spy mantane floor.
Oh, my God!
I think I'll eat this forever.
Oh, hey, that ribbon... I wanted you to put it on Yuna.
What's that?
I wanted Yuna to have it.
I bought it.
They're good!
Yes, and I also bought a microphone.
Yeah, I wanted you to get back at me.
I got you a set. You can do it later.
Oh, are you okay?
You're making eye contact, Tarren.
The little kids are working so hard.
I'm eating a candy bar.
I'm always working.
I know, right?
It's a rare sight now, isn't it?
These two sitting together.The sight of these two sitting there.
They're moving.
Yeah, the Chibi's over there moving
Plus Lung-chan is standing up.
It's a rare sight, folks.
Maybe just because it's that video, everybody's trying to work.
That's a huge relief with all this rain.
Edo Beans are relieved too.
Oh, I thought they were working, but everyone was just eating snacks and looking for playthings
Serious. Serious.
Video LTD
Video la k
Ratsmellia with an invincible smile.
Oh, hey Yuna, turn around and do it.
More back back back
Her hair is so beautiful.
See, it's perfect now, isn't it?
You've got this cobo for me.
Here, this ribbon and this microphone.
I bought the set for Yuna so she could use it.
Wait, that's not good.
You're so cute. People say you're a genius.
See you later.
I can tell it's me.
Okay, let's get serious.
Who can say it's me?
Okay, I can roll the camera.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to put on makeup.
What was that? While you're still in shape. Oh, it's okay.
Boo-boo! What's the first thing idols do when they start out?
Oh, I'm going to go for it!
I'm okay with getting a little wet at the meeting... but I've got my minor in the way.
I'll devote myself to you with love, then I want you to be my fan... I'm not going to say it, I'm not going to say it.
I've got a lot of love for you!
Wanna sing?
What's this?
It's amazing!
It's starting to look like Irie.
I can see it.
It's Irie.
Oh, my God.
She's so cute!
She's so cute.
Here she comes.
Shouting to the sound of love. Everyone's waking up.
Goodbye, love, you don't even show up
You're not who you say you are
Oh, I see you.
LOL!
That's great.
I'll run with the wind.
With all of you.
Let's dance.
Two.
Two. Two.
Mr. Hatcherloo, if you're a cagush...Mr. Hatcholoo, if you're a cagush.
I'm looking for a long love affair.
I'll grow up before you know it.
I can't reach you.
I want you more
I want you I need you
I love you
Thank you very much.
What are you doing?
What?
It's getting hard on my arm.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it without a screwdriver.
Carbonated ending listings.
Couldn't there be some kind of carbonated battery in there?
I said there is.
Carbonic acid
Lots of soda.
Seltzer water?
Three soda pop.
And a screwdriver.
Ahhh...
It's got a microphone.
There you go.
I can barely feel it.
This one and this one.
Three soda bottles.
Three soda pop.
Oh, my God.
You can change the voice.
That's great.
This is a con-newsie.
And that's two seltzer bottles.
I can't take it anymore.
Not yet.
That's the one.
This is the one!
Hey, you little punk. - Hey, you little punk.
Sticky, sticky, sticky!
Mr. Popo!
Hey, Mr. Popo.
Hello.
Look, I've called the under.
I've called the under.
Oh, my God.
He's so cute.
Older kids.
Older kids
Older child
Cute
Still that guy
Wow.
Yes, sir.
Someone pass.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, shit.Oh, my God.
Two people?
Really?
Oh, please.
Look, look, look.
Oh, my gosh.
Mon-chan!
Stop, seriously.
Huh?
Like this.
This will be good next time.
Beautiful.
They say you look like a magical girl.
She says you look like a magical girl.
What?
I danced.
Hello, there.
Sticky, sticky, sticky.
What? Isn't it great?
What? It's on.
What?
What? Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
It went.
We're doing it here?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
He's so cute.
It's like a photo shoot.
Next time, we'll have a live photo with soap bubbles, right?
Take a picture of Roon-chan.
Turn around.
Take a picture of Lun-chan.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it at all.
I think this is the one.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's it.
Thank you for watching!
I want to take a picture of this.
I can just take a screencap of this.
Yeah, that's great.
I'm so hungry!
I think it's time to take a picture now.
Oh! Surprise!
Surprise, surprise. Okay, bye.
That's so cute.
Here's a cute little key.
I heard that the other day.
Look at that.
Oh, my God.
The microphone is bent.
You can do real karaoke.
Oh, my God.amazing (e.g. of strength)
amazing
That's great.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's got a great rhythm.
I want my head.
That's fun.
I'm going to pour a lot of this down your throat.
It smells so good.
That's what they say.
Let's do this.
Hold this.
Okay!
I don't think he's using the microphone.
It's him!
He's making a scene somewhere.
You're making too much noise.
We're our own people!
Love, love, love!
What you're seeing right now, right in front of you...
It's a real dream.
Let's do it... the best thing we can do.
With a catheter jump
Wow, wow, wow
Wow. Wow. Wow.
So look at that.
A whole lot of glass.
It's a game of twists and turns.
Always give it your all
You won't regret it
Wow, wow, wow, wow
You're the best
Yeah! Yeah!
To that bright future
With a jumper on top of a jumper on top of a jumper
Fly high
Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump!
Oh, wow. I'm growing.
It's great.
This is a great song, everyone, so please join in.
Maybe we'll sing it all summer!
Maybe! Maybe!
Drink me high, drink me high
High again, high again, high again
Shutterpuff looking up
Tamera mera mera mera mera
Everybody jumpy
high again high again high again
My heart once more
love's call that I've been waiting for
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Listen to me
Moo moo moo moo moo
So cute
I can rest
In my hand
You're here.
Is that it?What's that?
This is karaoke.
Here we go.
Everybody sing a little bit.
How about karaoke?
A Time for Nails
When I had nails.
You were so good
Sometimes
Everyone's Birthday
4 minutes
Three minutes.
Wow.
That's great.
My heart too.
This place is in trouble.
Faster than anyone.
Higher, higher, higher
Yes, in the blink of an eye
Yes, in a blink of an eye
I like it.
I'm melting
Turn around already
Yes, high again
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh my God, Dr. Pony!
Pony! Pony!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Over here!
I'm so wet.
You're in the picture.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Poof, poof, poof.
round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round and round
Cackle
Your red hair is
Cuckoo!
You like me, don't you?
You're so cute.
Just for today.
Shiny, Shiny, Shiny.
Oh, I'm scared!
Oh, no!
An-chan is scary
Shinji-chan
The path isn't so good
There...
There.
Everyone's buying something!
Pakurampa!
Same as always.
Congratulations!
We did it!
Congratulations.
Sunshine.
Huh.Huh.
How'd it go? Candling?
Suddenly.
Oh, my God.
Karaoke, right?
Introduce yourself.
I'll just introduce myself now.
My favorite self-introduction right now.
I'm in a mood.
What do you want to do in the summer?
Let's see...
I don't know.
Tell me your name.
I want to do something fun.
I'm Talen.
I'm Se-no.
I'm Enchara.
I'm Ichi Talen.
I am Next Rina
Se-no.
Rina-chan, come here!
Guitar Beauty!
Who is it?
You must be the most loving person in the world.
First of all, Yuna-chan.
Yuna-chan, please.
Yuna-chan.
I'll do my best to arrange the world's best today.
I'm sure you're right.
Wow!
The creeder...
Ahhh...
Something happened.
I think something happened.
Something's not right.
Do it all!
Introducing the octopus?
Next.
Great, Anka.
Yes, from Yamaguchi Prefecture.
I'm Kitamiyu.
I hate singing and dancing.
But I like coke sans.
I'm Kitamiyu.
Yay!
Yes, Miyagi's famous food is here!
My favorite Tika and today, I'm going to raise the tension for the rest of my preparation time!
Yuna Ramen!
Yuna ramen!
An idol with the potential to become a great star like in a boys' manga
Fashion group, the name of which is
Popular Lidwaffan
I like it now.
Oh!
Good job, sir.Thanks for your time.
Is everyone having a good time?
Yes, I am.
Oh, my God, I'm really tired.
What the hell is this?
The other side of idols.
The other side of a regular show.
It's too much!
Is that a break?
Pan-pan-pan-pan!
I can play it wirelessly.
Thank you... for the tickets.
No, thank you.
Thank you.
I thought you'd be excited about this.
Oh, it's nothing.
I bought it because I thought it would make you excited.
I'm looking for the source.
You can take a break.
Fuji.
There's little Fuji.
Are your legs feeling better now?
They're fine.
They're wet.
Like, uh-huh.
That's great.
You should try this.
You can do effects with that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I do.
Always, right?
Always?
Look for it!
There's a guy. I'm already on him.
What's that?
This.
This?
Uh, it's saying "don't, don't, don't, don't.
They're saying "don't, don't, don't.
We all went shopping yesterday for the delivery.
We bought more stuff to play with than we could possibly use in a day.
Oh, look, look, look.
Oh, I've got a lot of grown-ups here.
I really want to play idols, but they'll disappear
Hey, I stepped in a puddle
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Oh, no, I'm going to be a bucket.
Oh, I see Kaya's face.
Shunk!
Shun!
Sorry for being so cute.
Here we go.
I'm sorry I was born.
Ah,
I tried to play catch with Mon-chan.
I'll do a version with Lun-chan later, so wait for me.
Great!
That's great.
This is fun!
It's fun.
Okay, Lun-chan's point of view, Lun-chan's version!Then, Rung-chan's eyes, Rung-chan's version.
She thought I was tacky.
Lame? This is cute.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Hikaru, I'm going to throw it.
It's cute!
So cute!
Nice.
I'll throw every time, Hikaru.
Throw it down.
Point it at me, sis.
Tightly!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's fucked up.
Thank you. Thank you.
Will you ask me again?
No, not at all.
YouTubers.
I like it.
I like your points.
Thank you.
Hanakin Couple
Hanakin Couple.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to lend this to you and put it on.
Wow!
Vegetables and beef tongue!
There's such a thing as beef tongue!
Look, look.
Wow!
Screen screen screen
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
You like it?
Yeah, it's okay. It's okay.
All right, Mr. Downstairs, this is for you.
Oh, yeah.
Did you see that?
Ghost.
A ghost.
Haunted.
Haunted...
Shine...
Can you hold that for me, staff?
Camera.
He's playing alone.
Oh, he's so cute!
Good for you!
Guys! Guys!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
That's it!
It's the same one.
It's okay.
What?What?
Not here?
Give it to me.
Maybe it's the wrong size.
It didn't fit.
Who was that?
Hajime-san?
Is that you?
It's the wrong size.
Wrong size?
So it's impossible?
Sparrow rice?
Yeah, it's yellow.
Look, it's yellow.
I'll cut it off.
Okay, let's not do that.
You want some of this?
Yeah, that's good.
Okay, okay.
Everybody, get on the rice.
Come on.
This will be real in the morning.
Yes, it is.
Fun, very, this.
Barikiri all at once.
You guys should get one of these.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Buy it?
Fanny's.
If we take a picture from here, we'll all be in it.
Do you want to draw a little?
Ring.
Oh, hold it right here.
Now we've got Jenny.
You want to paint it yourselves?
Wow, I've been waiting for you.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God.
I want to take a picture of this.
I can see so much.
The neck below this one is pretty awesome, too.
Oh, my God.
Can you point me to another one?
Yes, ma'am.
When not to hug me.
Let's see...
Roon, come closer to Yuna.
And you, Grandma...
Yuna-chan
Yuna-chan, Yuna-chan
Here we go!
Cheese!
You're so low!
It's been a while since I've been here.
It's an airport.
Just drinks.
I'll be right back.
Go for it.
It's getting pretty warm. It's steamy.It's getting pretty warm. There's steam coming out.
It's just warming up.
Maybe we can use it now.
It's on fire.
I like it when you say that.
I'm gonna get you a drink, Fee.
What do you want?
A drink.
Well, who wants calpis?
Yes, I do.
What? Like this?
Yes.
Then I'll listen to the other side and do it already.
Thank you.
What would you like?
Coke.
Definitely.
Thank you.
Cora is a good person.
I can definitely just see it.
De captain.
Who wants tea?
Well tea.
I like this yellow-green one.
I'll help you then.
Tea.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I've gone to the trouble of taking off the labels.
Here you go, Kanenori-san.
But you know what the Calpis guy says...
The orange one
Oron or Oron?
Or Oron or Ocha?
Well... Well... Well...
Good tea.
And well... well... well... well... well... well...
Who's orange?
Just in.
Three minutes.
Not yet.
There's someone in orange.
I thought he was there, but he's huge.
Thank you.
And no, it's not tea.
Six more hours.
That's great.
Don't you want a Coke?
Did you get the Coke?
I did.
I've got work to do.
Yeah.
Good job, guys.
Oh, cool.
That's great.
I can't believe you're in such a hurry.
I think you're good.
And Yu...
And Yu.
Yu, I couldn't write it myself.
SomedayWhen.
Definitely.
Stay up late at night, for sure.
And everyone else, I guess.
Hey, did you get something?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Is this the one on the oysters?
Oh, two.
I have one of these.
I don't have one of those.
Here, come on.
Okay, choo-choo-choo.
Rice in a pot is really good.
Rice cooked in camp and rice cooked in a pot.
I'm going to cut off a little bit of the distribution.
Here, I'm kind of erasing the screen of my phone.
I'll copy and paste it right away.
I'm going to cut the feed.
See you later.
He's going to change the URL.
I'll be in touch again.
See you soon.
I may not deliver.